And now with an editorial,
here's Squidward Tentacles.
现在有了一篇社论，
这是章鱼哥的触手。
Good evening.
晚上好。
Everyone continues
to be horrible,
大家继续
变得可怕，
and I've got the proof.
我有证据。
Here are my
"Beefs of the week."
这是我的
“本周精选牛肉。”
Our first beef is,
我们的第一块牛肉是，
this filthy foodie always eats
before he pays.
这个肮脏的美食家总是吃东西
在他付款之前。
Then he gives me a handful
of money
然后他给了我一把
钱的
slathered in slimy grease.
涂满了粘稠的油脂。
Horrible. Next.
可怕。下一个。
Ho-Ho, boy, do I have a beef
with this annoying guy.
嗬嗬，孩子，我有牛肉吗
和这个烦人的家伙。
What?
什么？
I'm done?
我受够了？
But I've got 47 more "beefs."
但我还有 47 块“牛肉”。
Typical.
典型的。
Coming up next,
it's "Fun-believable" with...
接下来，
这是“有趣且可信”的……
Rube Goldfish?
鲁布金鱼？
Huh?
啊？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
That guy puts mustard
in his milkshakes.
那家伙放了芥末
在他的奶昔里。
Horrible.
可怕。
Whoa, whoa, hey, watch it.
哇哇哇，嘿嘿，看一下。
Well, hello, everybody.
嗯，大家好。
I'm Rube Goldfish,
and today we'll be exploring
我是鲁布金鱼
今天我们将探索
the amazing and unknown
Bikini Bottom.
令人惊奇和未知的
比基尼下装。
what you are about to see
您将要看到的内容
is gonna make you say,
"That's Fun-believable."
会让你说，
“这很有趣，令人难以置信。”
Uhh...
呃...
we're here at
Sandy Cheeks' Treedome,
我们现在在
桑迪奇克斯的树顶，
because--
- Um, excuse us, Rube, but...
因为——
- 嗯，对不起，鲁布，但是……
The public restroom is
right around the corner, boys.
公共卫生间是
就在拐角处，孩子们。
No, Patrick and I
have something to show you.
不，帕特里克和我
有东西要给你看。
It's "Fun-believable."
这是“有趣且可信”。
Really?
真的吗？
Well, that's just what
I'm looking for.
嗯，就是这样
我正在寻找。
Show us what you got.
向我们展示您得到了什么。
Okay, you ready?
好吧，你准备好了吗？
- I think so.
- This is our chance.
- 我想是的。
- 这是我们的机会。
Oh, you don't have to tell me, SpongeBob.
噢，你不必告诉我，海绵宝宝。
All right. All right.
All right.
好的。好的。
好的。
- Is he still there?
- Let's check.
- 他还在吗？
- 让我们检查一下。
- Okay, he's still there.
- You ready?
- 好吧，他还在那儿。
- 你准备好了吗？
Yeah.
both: One, two...
是的。
两者：一、二……
We're ready!
我们准备好了！
We're not ready.
我们还没准备好。
Okay, come back when you are.
好吧，有空就回来吧。
Must be camera shy.
一定是害羞相机。
Yipe!
哎呀！
Would you look at that?
Amazing.
你会看一下吗？
惊人的。
Whoa!
哇！
Howdy do, Rube?
你好，鲁布？
Howdy, Miss Cheeks.
你好，奇克斯小姐。
Now, if the robotic arms weren't
"Fun-believable" enough,
现在，如果没有机械臂
足够“有趣-可信”，
I understand that you have
a secret skill
我明白你有
一项秘密技能
that nobody knows about.
没人知道。
That's right, Rube.
没错，鲁布。
I hold the squirrel record
for the most nuts
我保持松鼠记录
对于大多数坚果来说
stored in my cheeks.
储存在我的脸颊上。
Wow. Can you give us
a demonstration?
哇。你能给我们吗
示威？
Sure can.
I just happened to have
当然可以。
我只是碰巧有
some hazelnuts handy.
一些方便的榛子。
Ooh.
哦。
Ahh-ahh!
啊啊啊！
Wow, impressive.
哇，令人印象深刻。
I don't think it's possible
to fit any more than that.
我认为这是不可能的
适合更多的东西。
You ain't seen nuttin' yet.
你还没见过疯子。
Ahh-ahh-ahhh-ahhh.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊。
Wow.
哇。
Fun-believable.
有趣可信。
both: Oh, Rube?
两人：哦，鲁布？
We're ready.
We're ready. We're ready.
我们准备好了。
我们准备好了。我们准备好了。
Well, folks, it looks like--
both: We're ready. We're ready.
好吧，伙计们，看起来就像——
两人：我们准备好了。我们准备好了。
Ahh-ahh!
啊啊啊！
Ugh.
啊。
I think I have a nut-ache.
我想我有点头痛。
both: Sorry, Sandy.
两人：对不起，桑迪。
Hey, Rube,
should we come back later?
嘿，鲁布，
我们应该稍后再回来吗？
Yeah, later would be good.
是啊，以后就好了。
We're here
at Nosferatu's Castle.
我们在这里
在诺斯费拉图城堡。
Which is a Historical landmark
in Bikini Bottom, by the way.
这是一个历史地标
顺便说一句，在比基尼底部。
Well, thanks, Rube.
好吧，谢谢，鲁布。
But why are we here today,
Mr. Nosferatu?
但我们今天为何来到这里，
诺斯费拉图先生？
Could you give us a hint?
你能给我们一个提示吗？
The master wants to
show you his--
主人想要
给你看他的——
heh-heh-heh--
pain-reaction--
嘿嘿嘿——
疼痛反应--
oh,
I mean chain-reaction machine.
哦，
我的意思是链式反应机。
Ugh!
啊!
So how does this
crazy contraption work, anyway?
那么这是如何做到的
无论如何，疯狂的装置工作？
Okay, Master, let it roll.
好吧，主人，就让它滚吧。
Oh. Oh, my. Ha-ha-ha.
哦。哦，我的。哈哈哈。
Ohh.
哦。
Heh-heh-heh. Wow.
呵呵。哇。
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
哈哈哈。
Mmm, snackies.
嗯，零食。
Ugh! Hee-hee-hee.
啊!嘻嘻嘻。
The master says,
大师说，
Rube's show is brought to you
by Fizzy Fangs Soda.
Rube的表演给你带来了
碳酸毒牙苏打水。
It tickles my teeth,
Heh-Heh-Heh.
看得我牙齿痒痒的
呵呵。
Fellas, that was truly
Fun-believable.
伙计们，这确实是
有趣可信。
both:
We're ready for you, Rube
两者：
我们已经为你准备好了，鲁布
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
both: No.
两人：没有。
I guess their moment
has passed... away.
我猜他们的时刻
已经过去了。
Whoo!
呼！
We're here with "Baby Prunes."
我们带着“小西梅”来了。
Now, you're the oldest resident
of Bikini Bottom.
现在，你是最年长的居民
的比基尼底部。
Isn't that right?
是不是这样？
What are you, a cop?
你是什​​么人，警察？
Ma, behave.
妈，乖点吧。
He's interviewing me, Mary,
so shut up.
他正在采访我，玛丽，
所以闭嘴。
You are too much.
你太过分了。
Honey, you should have seen me
70 years ago
亲爱的，你应该看看我
70年前
when I was middle-aged
and wild.
当我人到中年的时候
和野生的。
You're putting me on.
你这是在给我装逼
How could a sweet little old
lady like you ever be wild?
怎么可能是一个可爱的小老头
女士像你一样狂野吗？
That sounds like a challenge.
这听起来像是一个挑战。
Holy helicopters.
神圣的直升机。
We are flying over
Bikini Bottom,
我们飞过
比基尼下装，
and the view is spectacular.
景色非常壮观。
Hello.
你好。
Hi, Rube.
嗨，鲁布。
Baby Prunes, I've never seen
someone your age
梅子宝宝，我没见过
与你同龄的人
so amazingly active.
如此活跃。
You call this active?
I'll show you active.
你管这叫主动？
我会向你展示活跃的。
Ah-ha!
- Whoa-oh-oh!
啊哈！
- 哇哦哦！
Mrs. Prunes, you don't have to
go this fast to impress me.
普鲁内斯女士，你不必
走这么快是为了给我留下深刻印象。
This is your captain speaking.
这是你们的队长在讲话。
We're going down again.
我们又要下去了。
Eh... ohh!
呃……哦！
Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
哇哦哦哦！
Whoa!
哇！
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh,
ahhh!
哦-哦-哦-哦-哦，
啊啊！
Uh, that was the furthest thing
from Fun-believable.
呃，那是最远的事情
来自有趣可信。
You could have fooled me.
你本来可以愚弄我的。
Huh? Flapping Yaps at 12:00
啊？ 12:00 拍打雅普
Whoa-oh!
哇哦！
Ha-ha! Huh?
哈哈！啊？
This thousand-boat pileup
might be the greatest tragedy
这千船连环相撞
可能是最大的悲剧
to ever befall Bikini Bottom.
永远降临比基尼底部。
And I just want to thank
my Great Gram-Gram
我只想感谢
我伟大的格拉姆
for flying the copter today.
今天驾驶直升机。
She is the oldest citizen
in Bikini Bottom at 115.
她是最年长的公民
比基尼泳裤 115。
Mwah!
哇！
You are not the oldest citizen
in Bikini Bottom.
你不是最年长的公民
在比基尼底部。
You're only 115.
I'm 116.
你才115岁。
我116岁了。
Ooh, you fibber.
哦，你个胡言乱语。
If I wasn't your elder,
I'd pop you right in the beezer.
如果我不是你的长辈
我会把你直接扔进beezer。
I'm the oldest.
我是最年长的。
Oh-oh-oh-oh!
哦-哦-哦-哦！
I challenge you
to a copter duel.
我向你挑战
直升机决斗。
Oh, it's on,
like my hearing aid.
哦，已经开启了，
就像我的助听器一样。
Copter duel?.
直升机决斗？
No!
不！
This just in.
这个刚进去
TV news anchor Perch Perkins
电视新闻主播珀奇·帕金斯
jumped out
of a helicopter today.
跳出来
今天的直升机。
Whoa!
哇！
This is a no-fly zone, sister.
这是禁飞区，姐姐。
Whoa-oh-oh!
哇哦哦！
Hey, you. Get off of my cloud.
嘿，你。离开我的云端。
I'm the oldest.
我是最年长的。
I'll have to change the name
of this show
我得改个名字
这个节目的
from "FUN-believable" to...
ahhh!
从“有趣可信”到...
啊啊！
Ohh!
哦！
Oh-oh-oh-oh!
哦-哦-哦-哦！
Whee!
哎哟！
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha!
啊哈哈哈哈！
Time to go home, you two.
你们两个该回家了。
Yeah, that's enough excitement
for today.
是啊，够兴奋了
今天。
Aww.
哇。
I'm the oldest.
我是最年长的。
I am the oldest.
I'm the oldest.
我是最年长的。
Huh, I guess she was
the oldest.
呵呵，我猜她是
最古老的。
But I'm the oldest now.
但我现在是最年长的了。
Well, we've come to end
of our show, everybody,
好吧，我们已经结束了
我们的节目，大家，
and I just want to tell ya
how Fun-be--
我只想告诉你
多么有趣——
We're ready, Rube.
我们准备好了，鲁布。
It's now or never, fellas.
要么现在，要么永远，伙计们。
Take it away.
把它拿走。
Ahh.
啊。
Ahh!
啊！
Doink!
多因克！
Wow.
哇。
Whoa.
哇哦。
both: Ta-da!
两人：哒哒！
Ooh-hoo!
Now, that's Fun-believable.
哦呼！
现在，这很有趣-可信。
Horrible.
可怕。
Click.
点击。